Her Smell is a drama, music film directed by Alex Ross Perry.
A self-destructive punk rocker struggles with sobriety while trying to
recapture the creative inspiration that led her band to success.
Becky Something, played by Elisabeth Moss.
Crassy Cassie, played by Cara Delevingne.
'Dirtbag' Danny, played by Dan Stevens.
Marielle Hell, played by Agyness Deyn.
Ali van der Wolff, played by Gayle Rankin.
Roxie Rotten, played by Ashley Benson.
Her Smell is a 2018 American drama film written,
co-produced and directed by Alex Ross Perry.
It stars Elisabeth Moss, Cara Delevingne, Dan Stevens, Agyness Deyn, Gayle Rankin, Ashley Benson,  Amber Heard, Dylan Gelula, Eka Darville and Lindsay Burdge
and follows Moss as fictional rock star Becky Something, whose band experiences brief fame but is broken up by her self-destructive behavior.
Her Smell had its world premiere at the Toronto International Film Festival on September 9,
2018, and had its general release on April 12, 2019, by Gunpowder & Sky.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics,
who particularly praised Moss's acting.
The film explores themes of concert, drug abuse, punk
rock, recording studio, addiction.
The tone is emotional.